你好啊
Oh, hey.
能点菜了吗
You ready?
偶不能 偶真的不能
I can't. I just can't.
每个第一次来这里的客人都有这感觉
Everyone feels like that the first few times you eat here.
就跟海洛因一样 吸食后难受
It's like heroin. It makes you sick,
让你觉得"我下次不会再吸了"
and you think,"I'll never do that again,"
结果就上瘾到现在
and here we are.
不是 我们放项目上圆梦网了
No, we put our project on Kickstarter,
我们正要拿到一笔大款项呢
and we're getting major funding right now.
偶不能 偶真的不能[相信]啊
And I can't. I just can't.
圆梦网 就是那个
Kickstarter-- that's the website
网民送钱给那些现实生活中
where strangers give money for crap
没人会投资的狗屁项目的网站吧
that no one in the real world would invest in, right?
没错 但我们的项目不是狗屁
Exactly, but our project isn't crap.
是超屌好吗
It's bananas.
我们设计了有握把的蜡烛
We design candles with arms.
偶不能 我也不能了...
I can't. I just can't.
你难道没有个激情的梦想吗
Don't you have a passion project--
一个你一直很想做的事情
something you've always wanted to do?
对啊 你总不会想当一辈子的女服务员吧
Yeah, you can't just want to be a waitress your whole life.
其实呢
Actually...
我还真有个圆梦计划
I do have a Kickstarter idea.
想"圆"我想踢爆你们屁股的"梦"
I'd like to start kicking your asses!
你知道我们干活是为了挣小费吧
You know we work for tips, right?
这两个就当老娘放她们一马吧
Yeah. This one got away from me.
大家听好了 今天是周二
Okay, listen up, it's Tuesday,
我与马丁·路德·金一样 都有一个梦想
And like Martin Luther King, I have a dream.
今晚你得干其他活儿
Tonight you will do side work.
等等 姑娘 我还10分钟才开工呢
Hold up, girl. I have ten minutes till my shift starts.
麦克斯 你太不礼貌了
Max, that is not appropriate.
我是你老板 不许叫我"姑娘"
I'm your boss. Don't call me "girl"
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
行 你想玩是吧 那咱们来玩
Okay, you want to play? I'll play.
先生你好 你好啊 大汉子
Hey, sir. Hey, big manny man.
怎么不把你的鸡鸡亮给我瞧瞧
Why don't you show me your penis?
阿憨 你明知道我没有鸡鸡
Han, you know I don't have a penis.
这是我们两个唯一的共同点啊
It's the only thing we have in common.
卡洛琳呢
Where's Caroline?
在后面我们小蛋糕店里
In the back at our cupcake shop.
为什么你们不等这边的工作结束了
Why you don't open your walk-up window
才开你们的小店
Till you close here at night?
她先一步开始干"别的活儿"
She's getting a jump on our side work.
我们不能两边都干啊
What? We can't do ours and yours.
放松嘛 玛德丽[女性名]
Relax, Marjorie.
麦克斯 你就接着挑衅我
Keep it up, Max,
有天我会亮我的鸡鸡给你看的
and one day I will show you my penis.
你会后悔[觉得可怜]
And you'll be sorry.
是的 我会的
Yes. Yes, I will.
够了 新规矩
That's it! New rule!
不许再取笑老板
No more making fun of the boss!
阿憨不许我们再乱给他取绰号了
Han doesn't want us calling him names anymore.
要是不想被取绰号
It's like, if you don't want to be called names,
就别长成那副德行吗
don't look like that.
* Disclosure - 《When a fire starts to burn》
为什么打开窗口了 那些人在干嘛
Why is the window open? What is all that?
我没破产"死"的话 那就是我
It's me, if I had lived.
天啊 你看到那一架子衣服[一对大奶]了吗
Oh, my God. Did you see that rack?
何止看到 我还得整天挂着走呢
See it? I have to carry it around all day.
我已经每天都穿
I've been wearing the same clothes
同样的那几套衣服两年了
every day for two years.
我知道这是你梦想场景
Now, I know that's your dream scenario,
但这对我就跟惊悚片一样
but to me, it's a horror show.
那去买新衣服啊
Go get new clothes.
去街角那家店
Just go to the place around the corner
买点便宜新衣服
and buy some cheap ones.
麦克斯 那些衣服是按"磅"计价的
Max, they sell clothes by the pound.
所以人家叫"潮流磅磅棒"啊
That's why it's called the Fashion Pound,
就是这样才超酷啊
and that is why it is awesome.
我很乐意"割舍"很多方面的东西了
Look, I'm willing to cut a lot of other things,
包含"割"腕
including my wrists,
但我要上好材质的衣服
but I need quality clothes.
这裤子就是因为材质好
The only reason I've been able to wear these pants every day
才耐得住我天天穿啊
is because they're quality.
还得配合大量除臭清新剂
Well, that and a lot of Febreze,
这也让我想起
which reminds me...
我以前身上散发着大钞香
I used to smell like money.
现在只剩硬币味吧
Now I smell like pennies.
麦克斯 你也该来一发了
And, Max, you need a hit.
喷吧
'Breze me.
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
看到高级时装模特拍摄了吗
Did you see the high-fashion model shoot?
我当年在波兰 因为太矮不能当模特
I was too short to be a model in Poland.
看来我也只能十全九美了
Well, I guess you can't have it all, right?
我闻到了除臭清新剂味吗
Do I smell Febreze?
那是我第二爱的香味
That's my second-favorite scent.
我第一爱的香味就在那里呢
Oh, and there's my first-favorite scent.
苏菲 你好啊
Hey, Sophie.
抱歉 我们见过面吗
I'm sorry. Have we met?
我时常记不起我再也不想见到的人的脸
I'm not good with faces that I never want to see again.
怎么了
What happened?
你们不是说当朋友吗
I thought you guys were gonna be friends.
关系一团乱 笑中藏飞刀
Yeah, messed-up, passive-aggressive friends
偶尔打一炮的朋友关系
who occasionally sleep together,
就像瑞安·西克雷斯特与西蒙·考威尔那样
Like Ryan Seacrest and Simon Cowell.
我知道你是在玩哪招了
Oh, okay, I see what you're doing.
你是在装我们没有用电影角色名
You're pretending like we don't have
来称呼我们的性器官吗
movie-character names for our private parts.
再见了 女士
Well, good-bye, Miss,
替我向道菲尔太太问好
and give my regards to Mrs. Doubtfire.
好的 ET 回家去吧
Okay, E.T., go home!
姑娘们 这是你们的信
Here's your mail, girls.
麦克斯 苏菲买了新包
Max, Sophie had a new purse.
大家都有新的东西
Everybody has something new.
连公车上的流浪女都有个新发夹
Even the homeless lady on the bus had a new barrette,
虽然她双脚都开裂了
and even though her feet were split open,
我还是好嫉妒
I still felt jealous.
这不是账单呢
Oh, this is not a bill.
真新鲜
Now, that's a first.
"我们要赠送给您一台新手机
"We are offering you a new phone,
因为您手上的老型翻盖手机已经落伍了"
as older flip-model phones such as yours have been degraded."
他们现在开始羞辱手机了吗
They're slut-shaming phones now?
我不想要任何新东西
I don't want a new anything.
我喜欢我的老翻盖手机
And I like my old flip.
裤子公司怎么不给老娘寄封信来说
Where's my damn letter from the pants company,
"姑娘 你裤子都被你穿累了
saying, "Girl, those things are tired--
免费送你条新的吧"
Here's a new pair for free"?
你想要免费的东西
If you want something for free,
怎么不跟其他人一样上圆梦网呢
why don't you just go on Kickstarter like everyone else?
你不能在上面弄钱去买衣服啊
You can't use it for clothes.
可以吗
Can you?
要是能 我可以吗
And if you can, can I?
为啥不行 买衣服都没握把[手臂]蜡烛蠢
Why not? It's no stupider than candle arms.
如果那些蜡烛真有手臂
Now, if the candles had real arms
而且可以扇白痴买家的巴掌
and could slap the idiots who bought them,
那我绝对会投资
I'd invest in that.
麦克斯 我们一无所有
Max, we have nothing,
如果有人愿意白送我们东西
And if anybody is giving us something for free,
我们就得收下
We're taking it.
你得去拿那个免费手机
You are getting that free phone,
我也要去求免费衣服
And I am begging for free clothes.
形势正在好转啊
Things are looking up.
要不要先圆个有内裤穿的梦
You might want to Kickstart some underwear.
一看他们就没啥东西
Well, obviously, they don't have anything.
我们走吧
Let's go.
麦克斯 别走 我裤子又多裂了点
Max, stop. My pants just ripped some more.
我得再补一下
I have to fix them again.
好材质妹 你怎么不带这条裤子
Hey, quality, why don't you just take them
去办公用品卖场找人"缝补"一下
to Office Depot and get them tailored?
开逛吧
Let's shop.
惨了 又开始裂了
Uh-oh, they're ripping again.
我的水帘洞感觉到一股清风吹过
I feel a breeze up in my febreze.
有何能为你效劳
How can I help you?
你好啊 西安卓
Oh, hey. Hi, uh, Chiandra.
我可以去哪里弄个新翻盖手机
Where can I get a new flip phone?
让我想想
Mm, let me think.
危地马拉吧[第三世界国家]
Guatemala.
我会想你的 小机机
I'll miss you, phone.
我的心都要碎了
This is breaking my heart.
宝贝 别这样
Come on, boo.
这只是个手机 不是火星哥
It's a phone, not Bruno Mars.
把信给我吧
Now, I need that letter.
有的 就在我这边
Oh, here it is. I have it.
在我包里
It's in my purse.
她是怎么回事
What's her story?
她干嘛把手放屁股上
Why is her hand on her ass?
她订书针[胃束带]爆了
Her staples popped.
减肥胃束带吗
Lap band?
我亲戚也发生过
Happened to my cousin.
她喝个健怡七喜 然后就爆了
She had a diet 7 up and exploded.
然后她被诊断有多发性硬化
Then she got M.S.
但法官乔·布朗宣判
According to Judge Joe Brown,
这两者间并无关联
it was not related.
这台吧 我就拿这台
Uh, here, I'll just take this one.
别着急啊 慢慢看
Slow down, now. Take a look around.
你有各式各样的选择呢
You got a whole world of possibilities.
都拿起来摸摸试试
Pick 'em up, get a feel,
握在手里好好爽一把
Hold it in your hand for a while.
西安卓 这只是手机 不是火星哥
Chiandra, it's a phone, not Bruno Mars.
"轻松发短信
Oh, "Texting is easy
试试全新手指便利键盘"
with the new finger friendly keyboard."
我的手指绝对"友善"[便利]啊
My fingers are already too friendly.
问问我的四年级男友就知道
Ask my fourth-grade boyfriend.
这些范例短信越来越猥亵啦
These sample texts are getting kind of racy.
"坏消息 昨晚的避孕套好像破了"
"Bad news--I think the condom broke last night."
怎么会有人放这种短信在展示机上啊
Why would anyone put that on a display model?
那是我的手机
That's mine.
我不小心把它放在上面
I left it there by accident.
但不关你们的事
But that's not your problem.
告诉我 你需要什么功能的手机
Now, tell me, what are your phone needs?
我的需要很简单
Uh, my needs are simple.
我需要一台能给别人乱画胡子
I need a phone that can draw a mustache on people
偶尔会打给我妈再自动挂电话的手机
and occasionally will call my mother and hang up.
她还需要有好相机的手机
And she needs one with a good camera,
因为她要帮我录 讨新裤子的视频
because I have to film my video pitch for new pants.
我的屁股有个洞
I have a hole in my butt.
你知道谁的屁股上都有个洞 对吧
You know you're supposed to, right?
麦克斯 我好像又变处女了
Max, I might be a virgin again.
我爱死新手机了
I love my new phone!
又酷又红
It's so cool and red.
感觉充满了无限可能呢
It feels like anything could happen!
但应该是不会啦
But it probably won't.
我的第一个电话
My first call.
我该怎么做 该怎么接电话
What do I do? What do I do?
你好
Oh. Hello?
小妞 恭喜你啊 再见
Oh, hey, girl, good for you. Bye.
西安卓没怀孕
Chiandra's not pregnant.
麦克斯 你为什么在接西安卓的电话
Max, why are you taking calls from Chiandra?
你应该来拍我的视频啊
We have to do my video.
我必须得接她电话
I had to take her call.
她送了我好多免费软件
She gave me a bunch of free apps--
"愤怒小鸟" "涂鸦跳跃"
Angry birds, Doodle Jump.
如果你想看起来像只狗 也能弄哦
If you want to look like a dog, I could do that.
你看 这是圣伯纳犬版的我
Look, here's me as a St. Bernard.
看到我脖子上的酒桶了吗
See my neck keg?
我研究了下
Okay, I've done some research,
这些是别人想网上募款弄的东西
And here's some things other people want money for.
一个女人想募款弄一条新假腿
One woman wants money for a new leg.
页面往下
Scrolling.
等等 如果她只有一条腿
Wait. If she only has one leg,
她应该上"不能开踢网"吧
Shouldn't she be on can't-Kickstarter?
它们跟我中止合作了
Oh, I'm no longer working with them.
它们拒绝了我的计划
They denied my project.
它们说我不够有艺术感
Apparently, I'm not artsy enough
而且还有太多条腿
and have too many legs.
所以我上了"为己投资网"
So now I'm on Go Fund Yourself.
正好
Oh, perfect.
我也叫你去死好久了[音似]
I've been telling you to go fund yourself for years.
我新裤子的未来就靠这个视频了
The future of my pants hinges on the video pitch.
气氛语气一定要又可怜又凄惨
The tone needs to be sad and pathetic.
那你已经不用练习了
Uh, preparation done.
还有什么比前亿万富翁卡洛琳·钱宁
What's sadder than former billionaire Caroline Channing
上网求人给钱买裤子还惨
asking for money for pants?
他们不会知道是我
Oh, they're not gonna know it's me.
资助你的是恐怖组织吗
Are you being funded by Al-Qaeda?
他们要是真愿意资助 我也照收不误
If they're buying, I'm taking.
开拍
And action.
大家好 我不能告诉你们我的名字
Hi. I can't tell you my name,
我也不能露出我的真容 因为实在太难为情了
and I can't show you my face because I'm too ashamed.
可悲的是 我发现自己处于一种困境
Sadly, I find myself in a situation
就是我再也买不起衣服
where I am no longer able to provide myself
让自己在日常生活中
with the garments I need in order to be the best
看起来明艳照人
in my day-to-day life.
我知道这对各位来说可能不是个问题
I'm aware that this is not a problem for everybody.
停 等下 我得自拍一张
Stop, stop! I need to take a picture of myself
因为我现在处于人生最欢乐的时刻
having the most fun I've ever had.
你鼻子从你眼洞冒出来了
Your nose is coming out of your eyehole.
不行
No.
不行 麦克斯 不能停啊
No, no, no, Max, don't stop.
我正进入状态呢
I'm in a groove.
错 你进入的是纸袋
No, you're in a bag.
拜托让我拍一张你戴着纸袋的照片
Please let me take a picture of you in a bag
然后弄成狗的版本
and then turn it into a dog
这样就是俗称的"外带狗食袋"了
and then call it a doggie bag.
继续拍 麦克斯 我快不能呼吸了
Go, Max, I'm running out of oxygen,
而且我觉得袋子里有残留的芝士
and I think there was cheese in here.
开拍
And action.
如果我能达到目标
If I achieve my goal--
尤其是能凑够钱买一条高品质的裤子
specifically, a new pair of quality pants--
我答应大家 我一定会穿着那条裤子
then I promise I will give back to the community,
去回报社会
wearing said pants.
我只需募集一千五百美元
All I need is $1,500.
停 什么 一千五
Stop! Whoa! $1,500?
你要买多少磅的衣服呀
How many pounds of clothes are you getting?
听着 这是一条
Look, it's for one pair
德赖斯·范诺顿设计的丝织锦缎裤的价格
of amazing Dries Van Noten silk brocade pants--
超级好看的哦
super cute.
没错 这笔钱是不少
And, yes, it's a lot,
但我的投资者会得到相应的回报
but my investors will get something in return.
只要捐出5块钱
For $5, they will get
他们的内心将充满善意的喜悦
the feeling of goodwill in their heart.
放屁
Pbbt!
捐出10块钱 我会送他们
For $10, I'll send them a selfie
我穿着新裤子拍的自拍照
in the new pants that they bought.
捐20块的 我会送他们不穿裤子的自拍照
For $20, I'll send them a selfie without pants.
没有人会因为你所谓的"回报"白给你钱
Nobody is gonna give you money for the stuff you offered.
"内心充满善意的喜悦"
"Goodwill in their hearts"?
拜托 现在是互联网世界 人们都是衣冠禽兽
This is the internet. We're animals.
你说得对
You're right.
我想到个主意
I have an idea.
打开相机
Camera up.
开拍
And action.
我知道你们大多数人会觉得
I'm sure a lot of you are probably thinking,
"看这个被宠坏任性没大脑的蠢妞"
"Look at this spoiled, indulgent, clueless girl."
没错 我是这样想的
Well, I am.
而且你们甚至还会产生
And you're also probably thinking,
"天啊 真想冲上去给她一巴"的想法
"God, I want to slap her."
如你所愿 这个还真可以有
Well, guess what. You can!
只要捐出500块 你就可以亲自上门
For $500, you can come here
往我宠坏白痴的脸上使劲甩一巴
and slap my spoiled, clueless face.
停
And cut.
很不错吧
Pretty good, huh?
太有想法了 来 现在换你拿相机
Genius. Now, here, take the camera.
我要拍一个募集500块甩你耳光的短片
I want to film my video to raise $500 to slap you.
厄尔 瞧
Earl, look!
我其中一个赞助人刚又给我多捐了20块
I just got 20 more dollars from one of my backers!
让我把这件事搞清楚
Now, let me get this straight.
你管人们要钱
You just ask people for money,
然后他们就给你
and they give it to you--
全程没有用到武器吗
without using a weapon?
厄尔 我的绝望就跟刀割一样令他们就范吧
Well, Earl, I guess desperation cuts like a knife.
当白人 人生就是简单模式啊
Man, being White is easy.
我们准备好点餐了
Um, we're ready to order.
卡洛琳 我刚解开新道具糖果锤
Caroline, I just unlocked the candy hammer.
你能过来帮着俩妹子点餐吗
Can you go over there and take those girls' orders?
偶不能 偶真的不能
I can't. I just can't.
不是吧 我居然募集到一千块了
Oh, no way! I just hit $1,000!
这钱够买两条腿的布料了
That's almost both legs paid for!
你们好
Uh, hello?
你们俩当着我的面玩手机也太过分了吧
You're dinging and donging right in front of my face.
至少把手机调成震动行吗
Can't you at least put your phones on vibrate?
我不喜欢把工作和"乐趣"混在一起
I don't like to mix business with pleasure.
你们俩不许玩手机了 给我干活
You two need to be off your phones and working.
现在就去 不许回嘴[在背后说我坏话]
Now. And no back talk.
完全正确
Totally.
-完全正确 -完全正确
- Totally. - Totally.
我知道这是怎么回事了
Oh, I know what's going on.
你们用群聊来暗骂我
You're group-texting insults about me!
我们才没有
We are not.
我收到你们的短信了
I got your text!
阿憨的确看起来像《卑鄙的我》里面的小黄人
Han does look like those minion things in Despicable Me!
我还曾以为长到1米2后 就没人会欺负我了
And I thought bullying would end when I hit four feet.
天啊
Oh! Oh, my God!
我筹够钱买新裤子了
I'm getting my new pants!
刚收到了500块定金
I just got a $500 pledge!
有人想赏我巴掌 有人想赏我巴掌呢
Somebody wants to slap me! Somebody wants to slap me!
居然只有一个人吗
Just one person?
小憨憨说了 今晚不把其他活儿做完
Hey, Han insists we can't leave tonight
就不能下班回家
without doing our side work,
所以我把他的头改到穿着尿布的吉娃娃图上
So I made him into a chihuahua wearing a diaper.
快看你的手机
Check your phone.
卡洛琳
Caroline?
某人终于有新裤子啦
Someone got some new pants!
* 当激情开始四射 *
* When a fire starts to burn, right *
* 当激情开始蔓延 *
* And it starts to spread *
* 她会把这激情带回家 *
* She gonna bring that attitude home *
* 不想做自己不爽做的事 *
* Don't wanna do nothing, what they like *
* 当激情开始四射 *
* When a fire starts to burn, right *
我还没秀完呢
I wasn't finished!
但我看够了
No, I was.
麦克斯 我本来不想告诉你的
Max, I didn't want to tell you this,
但我曾私底下担心我的翘臀没了
but I was secretly worried my booty was gone.
但结果是裤子的问题
Turns out, it was just the pants.
老娘的翘臀还在 快拍个照留念
It's still there. Take a picture of it.
好的 给我看看
Okay, let me see.
太完美了
Perfect!
快群发给我们餐厅的群成员
Now, let's send a group-text to our diner family,
对了 你也要给我发一份
And I'd like you to copy me on that,
因为我想把这照片发给我监狱里的爸爸
because I want to send it to my dad in prison.
他肯定会为我感到骄傲
He'll be so proud.
是啊 他在监狱里肯定"见不着"什么屁股
Yeah, 'cause I'm sure he's not seeing any asses there.
你知道我喜欢这条裤子什么吗
You know what I love about these pants?
它让我的屁股看起来
How they make my butt look--
你关了窗户还能看见吗
Can you see it through the window?
我有新裤子啦
I got new pants.
厄尔 你收到我的短信了吗
Hey, Earl, you got my text, right?
你是说那条卡洛琳穿着新裤子
You mean that picture of Caroline in her pants
然后上面写着"我烦死她了"吗
that said, "I'm so sick of her"?
对 就是那条
I know, right?
哪天她弄到了新衣服 就直接杀了我吧
If she ever gets a new shirt, just kill me.
我懂你的意思 麦克斯 但我不敢相信
I hear you, Max, but I just can't believe
你还把这条短信发给她了
you included her on the text.
是啊 什么
Yeah. What?
天啊 我群发忘了踢她出群聊圈了
Oh, my god. I didn't take her off the chain.
如果你要说一个孩子坏话
I mean, if you're gonna trash a child,
一定得先把她踢出圈子啊
you got to take her off the chain.
瞧 厄尔 新裤子来了
Look, Earl, they're here!
瞧你捐的10块钱给你什么好处
Look what your $10 is buying you!
不想看 不想知道
Uh-uh, not looking. Don't want to know.
我要自己退出这圈子
I'm taking myself off the chain.
卡洛琳
Uh, hey, Caroline.
-你有收到我的短信吗 -还没
- Uh, did you get my text? - Not yet.
餐馆前门的手机信号很差
The front of the diner is a bad reception area.
别看 别看
Uh, no, no, no, no.
别拿手机出来了
Don't reach for that.
可能只是安珀警报
It's probably just an Amber alert.
你干嘛怪怪的
Why are you acting weird?
你是不是嫉妒我有新裤子
Oh, are you jealous of my new pants?
不是 但是我可能在短信里
No, but I may have texted something about you
乱说了你一些事
that I didn't mean,
所以拜托不要看你的手机
So just please don't look at your phone.
好的
Uh, okay.
如果说的是坏话 那我也不想看
If it's something bad, I don't want to see it anyway.
她一定会看的 对吧 厄尔
She's gonna look at it, isn't she, Earl?
是我肯定会
I would.
她刚看了
She just did.
你烦死我了
You're so sick of me?
闹着玩嘛
'cause it's funny!
"我烦死你了"
"I'm so sick of you"
你懂的 就闹着玩而已
You know, said funny.
你了解我的嘛 不信问厄尔
You know how I am. Ask earl.
厄尔 救我
Earl, help.
我已经退出圈子了
Oh, I am off the chain.
奥列格 救我
Oleg, help.
我在车上等你
I'll be in my car.
瞧 阿憨来了
Oh, look, look! Here's Han!
他知道我经常开玩笑闹着玩
He knows how I'm always just joking.
阿憨 别问原因快点头
Han, nod your head and don't ask why.
不要 上次你让我这么做
Oh, no, last time you asked me to do that,
结果我跟得了白化病的人约会
I wound up on a date with an albino.
那后来是谁没给对方回电的
And who didn't call who back?
我都不知道她们哪里来的自信
I don't know how they're so confident.
麦克斯 你说你烦我
Max, you said you were sick of me.
你干嘛这么生气
Oh, why are you so upset?
我经常对你说一些更难听的话
I say worse things to you all the time.
昨天我还说你可怜又可悲
Yesterday I said you were sad and pathetic.
但那是当着我的面
But that was to my face.
我真不敢相信你居然在背后说我坏话
I can't believe you talk about me behind my back.
这是我不好 对不起
It's bad. I am sorry.
你要怎么惩罚我
What can I do?
打我 揍我
Hit me. Punch me.
还是告诉我妈我的地址
Tell my mother where I live.
恭喜你 麦克斯
Congratulations, Max.
现在你就像我以前的朋友
Now you're like all my old girlfriends,
专在背后说我坏话
talking behind my back.
别看了 删掉它
Stop looking at that. Delete it.
这不是我的真实想法
This is not what I think.
-我没有烦你 -真的吗
- I'm not sick of you. - Really?
可我看着这几个字 就觉得你的确是烦我
'cause when I see it in writing, it feels like you are.
这不是我 是这手机在作怪
It's not me. It's this phone.
它把我本来就丑恶的那面给揭露出来了
It brought out the ugliness that was kind of already there.
你看
There!
因为它伤害了你 所以我毁掉它
I killed it because it hurt you.
我发誓我不是故意的
I swear I didn't mean it.
你一定要相信我
You have to believe me.
没关系 麦克斯
It's fine, Max.
我感觉我要吐了
I feel like I'm gonna throw up.
瞧 我把我的手机炸了
There... I french-fried my phone.
你还想我怎么样
What else can I do?
真的 这是科技的错
I mean, really, it is technology's fault.
它让我们彼此翻脸
It's turning us against each other.
卡洛琳 我发誓 我再也不会意外说出
Caroline, I swear, I will never accidentally say
任何我不是真心说你的坏话
anything about you again that I never meant.
我得开始干活了 没关系啦
I have to get ready for work. It's fine.
别这么说
Stop saying that.
拜托不要再说"没关系"了
Please stop saying it's fine.
"没关系"就是有关系
"Fine" doesn't mean fine.
形容事情好坏的顺序是很棒 很好 还行
The scale goes great, good, okay,
不行 我讨厌你 没关系
not okay, I hate you, fine.
如果"没关系"真的是没关系 那当然是最好
If "fine" meant fine, that'd be great,
但它不是
but it doesn't, okay?
你说的对 的确有关系
You're right. It's not fine.
这太过分了 我受伤了
It sucks. I'm hurt.
你是我最在乎的人
You're the one person I care most about.
不 你才是我唯一让我最在乎的人
No, you are the one person I care the most about.
但现在感觉就不是那样
Well, right now it doesn't feel that way.
必须是那样
It has to feel that way!
你是我最好的朋友 卡洛琳
You are my best friend, Caroline!
我爱你
I love you.
天啊 现在我是真的要吐了
Oh, my god, now I'm really gonna throw up.
麦克斯 这是你第一次说"我爱你"吗
Max, is that the first time you said "I love you"?
不要看人家 人家害羞啦
Don't look at me. I'm embarrassed.
现在我们干嘛
Now what do we do?
所以你并不烦我吗
So you're not sick of me?
你是全世界我唯一
You are the only person in the entire world
不会觉得烦的人
I am not sick of.
卡洛琳
Caroline...
有个女的说花了钱要赏你巴掌
There's a woman here who said she paid to slap you.
如果早知道可以这样
If I had known it was an option,
我也参与捐款了
I would have thrown my name into that hat.
是时候把这个戴上了
Well, time to put this on.
那可是我价值500块的承诺啊
That's my $500 pledge.
-我去吧 -什么
- I'll go. - What?
我替你挨巴掌 我活该
I'll take it. I deserve it.
你已经被我扇了一耳光了
You've already gotten a slap in the face from me.
但她要见的是我
But she's expecting to see me.
错 她要见的是一个戴着纸袋的
No, she's expecting to see a clueless woman
白痴女人
wearing a paper bag.
虽然我本计划是20 25年后
And even though I wasn't planning
才打算变成这样的女人
on becoming that woman for another 20, 25 years,
但今天算我欠你的
I owe you.
真的吗 你不打算阻止我吗
Seriously? You're not gonna stop me?
不打算
Nope.
对了 麦克斯
And, Max...
我也爱你
I love you too.
我真是烦死你了
I'm so sick of you.